Wisam Diefallah

Mississauga, ON wisamdiefallah3_vgi@indeedemail.com (647)-822-7073

My comprehensive experience in customer service and leadership ensures excellent work ethic and interpersonal competence. My passion for establishing and maintaining quality customer relationships motivates me to join the workforce where I hope to share my diverse knowledge and skill set as a member of your hardworking team!

Work Experience

Customer Service Representative

Scotiabank

March 2019 to Present

- * Processed cash and check transactions, evaluated potential fraudulent claims, and facilitated 130+ weekly customer account inquiries
- * Personable, efficient service employed to establish rapport and guarantee an ideal customer experience
- * Coordinated work with supervisor to guarantee smooth operation of the branch and balance the vault which exceeded \$50,000

Supervisor

Absolute Auto

September 2015 to February 2019

- * Managed payroll, employee operations, and the invoicing of customer charges and accounts
- * Sourced and negotiated new inventory with vendors while overseeing daily store operations
- * Keen knowledge of services and products perfected while developing estimates for vehicle inspections

Sales Associate

Walmart Canada

August 2011 to September 2014

- * Honed problem-solving skills by settling customer complaints and encouraging employee collaboration
- * Developed professional communication skills by discussing staff efficiency and potential improvements with managers during weekly meetings
- * Ensured proper documentation is completed with respect to the receiving and return of goods

Sales Associate

Old Country Family Bakers June 2010 to July 2011

- * Coordinated baking deliveries to ensure timely service
- * Oversaw product inventory and quality control in adherence to the company's regulations
- * Refined interpersonal skills by solving customers' inquiries

Education

Diploma in Taxation, Accounting, Finance, Marketing

Sheridan College

September 2014 to August 2016

Skills

- Customer Care
- CSR
- Customer Service
- Call Center
- Customer Support